RESUME

ISHITA SINGH

U-11, Konark Campus, Viman Nagar, Pune-411014. Ph.no- 9607701333 iishitaa.singh@gmail.com

Strengths

- Good effective Communication skills.
- Efficient in Operations and management.
- Leadership quality.
- A quick learner.
- A good team player.
- Good computer knowledge.
- A hardworking attitude.
- Good time Management skills.

Employment

➤ Amazon India. Virtual Customer Support from Oct 2018 till Present date

Responsibilities

- Handling E-mails and responding to emails for North America and Rest of the World customers.
- Providing support to customers for issues related to Alexa and Amazon devices.
- Handling Prime Video issues and Appstore issues along with Twitch.
- Providing best customer service is the core deliverable.
- ➤ Vidya Singh & Associates. Manager from 2015 till 2018

Responsibilities

- Managing the overall office administration.
- Arranging client meetings.
- Keeping track of employee attendance and salary.
- co-ordinating with various vendors on site and off site as well.
- Visiting sites to keep a check on daily progress.
- ➤ Skillkraft Solutions. Sr. HR Manager from Feb 2013 till November 2014.

Responsibilities

- Handling a team of 10 People to achieve the set targets.
- Co-ordinating with Clients/ HR of companies for business needs.
- Screening/ Interviewing / Shortlisting candidates as per the requirement.
- Briefing/ Training candidates on soft skills, presentation, job summary.

- Keeping a track of overall office administration.
- Maintaining the track record of client payouts and receiving them on time.
- Attending / Arranging Client meetings for business development.

Educational Qualification

- Diploma in Travel and Tourism Studies. IGNOU, Pune.
- Bachelor of Economics,
 St. Mira's College, Pune.
- Diploma in Events and Advertisement,
 College of Events and Media, Pune.
- HSC (Passed in the year 2009), M.S Board, L.A.D College, Nagpur.
- SSC (Passed in the year 2007), C.B.S.E Board, Modern School, Nagpur.
- Diploma in Digital Marketing. Internshala, Pune.

Career Summary

- Result focused professional offering 5 years of Managerial experience.
- Good communication with consultative approach, strong negotiating skills, exceptional problem solving abilities, and a keen client needs assessment aptitude.
- Flexibility for adapting new work cultures with result focused attitude.

Personal Details

➤ Date of birth : 20th August 1991

> sex : Female

➤ Marital Status : Single

➤ Languages Known : Hindi, Marathi , English , French, Hebrew

➤ Hobbies : Travelling, Dance, Photography, Adventure sports, Outdoor sports.

➤ Extra-curriculum achievements: Events managed for different occasions, NCC cadet in school, Trekking camps attended, State-level basket ball player, Dance workshops attended, Weddings planned and executed end to end.

<u>Declaration</u>: I hereby do declare that the above mentioned particulars are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.